THE APARTMENT JOB
-Park Hae-kang! -Park Hae-kang! Park Hae-kang!
-Park Hae-kang! Park Hae-kang! -Park Hae-kang! Yeah!
Park Hae-kang! Park Hae-kang!
-Park Hae-kang! -Park Hae-kang!
-Yeah! Park Hae-kang! -Park Hae-kang! Park Hae-kang!
-Now presenting, True Value's LRRF -Park Hae-kang!
Park Hae-kang!
Recovered thanks to your sacrifice and cooperation!
Deposit,
And now your money, ladies and-
-Come on, hurry up! Show us! -Do it! Come on, just do it! You can
-Hurry up! -do it!
Come on.
Hey, what's going on. Come on.
Hey, stop messing around and show us.
Huh?
What all this?!
Mr. Park, have you forgotten why they call me the Lizard?
Cutting off my own tail is nothing to me.
As far as the money goes, don't worry, I'll take good care of it.
-Oh! -No, wait! What? What's happening?
What's happening! What is this?
But– But it– But it was all in here! Oh!
I can't see, try zooming in a little bit.
Oh! Th-there.
It's the Lizard, zoom in some more.
And next to him, ugh, that's Lee Chung-won's right hand man, that's
Mr. Kim.
So the Lizard joined forces with Lee Chung-won?
Oh, my goodness.
How could stab us in the back, that's so wrong!
Th-that old man must have lost his mind!
That prick Lee Chung-won
That's what he does.
He tried to bait me with 500 million to hand over the original ledger.
Do you think he enticed Mr. Hwang with a similar offer?
I almost forgot. Lee Chung-won offered me an expensive pent-
House suite that was over 80 pyeong.
Wait a second.
How come he didn't offer me anything?
Ugh, that's what's upsetting you right now? All of our money has been hijacked!
I'm upset about that too! I'm upset about that too!
I'm picking up the Lizard's phone signal.
Where is that jerk? I should just run him over with my car.
Wait a minute!
Don't you think it's strange?
Why would someone rob us of so much of our
Money, and leave their phone on?
Someone so good at being a ghost would never reveal their location.
Exactly. His first move would be ditching his phone, but look how steady that
-signal is. -Oh, really?
He's not running away.
He's baiting us.
Baiting?
Baiting how?
Lee Chung-won's baiting me there.
The Lizard's being used as a lure.
Why would you fall for this?
He's trying to trap you there!
I'm aware of that.
But a member
Of our family's there.
-Come on. -Let's go.
-You guys -Wait for me.
Please spare my life, please Chairman Lee!
I have something important to tell you.
Chairman Lee!
Chairman Lee.
I know my time might be up, but I have to let you know.
The-the truth is-
That my left leg is cramping so badly I can't stand it.
It's bent so badly-
I don't wanna die before I get this cramp outta my leg.
Do something to distract.
I tried to touch my tongue to the tip of my nose but that doesn't help!
Now both my leg and my tongue are cramping! Wait! Wait! Wait!
There's a chance that I might be somewhat claustrophobic. I did finally
Overcome my fear of heights but then I found out I was claustrophobic.
Come on shut up.
I really can't handle this!
How can a businessman be so untrustworthy?!
Huh?
I mean you said all I had to do was bring the money!
I have about thirty of my men
Blocking the front of Mr. Park's house.
They'll break down the door if push comes to shove.
They all like to play extremely dirty.
They're rough around the edges.
My men aren't going home until you leave with the money.
Look me in the eye.
I'll do it. I'll do it, please, I'll do it
Pl-please don't kill me.
And- you said you'd leave the others alone.
You don't seem to know how businesses work.
In the line of big business
One must always
Play dirty by default.
Trustworthy?
That's how you become a pawn.
A little blackmail
Some exploitation, and then betrayal.
Finding their weakness is key to doing good business.
Then um, this thing
-are you going to -Very good.
You've seen it in many movies, right?
We're going to pour concrete up to here,
We'll make sure it completely hardens
Then push it over the edge with my foot!
Park Hae-kang should be arriving about now
He won't be coming here.
Don't bother waiting, he won't come no matter what.
I mean, unless he's a complete idiot, why would he?
I took the LRRF and
Ra-ran away with it
So he won't come save me no matter what!
Park Hae-kang
Will be here.
Never, never!
You're wrong-you're wrong about that!
Park Hae-kang will arrive!
Lee Chung-won!
I'm a prophet.
Even though he knows it's a death trap,
He can't help himself but to walk into it.
Applaud the fool, everyone.
Clap your hands.
Lizard, are you okay?
You crazy bastard.
You dumbass. Why the hell did you,
Why the hell did you come here?
Why the hell'd you do something so stupid.
You messed with my family today.
For that, you're gonna die.
You got that backwards, you're going to die today.
You kidnapped my money.
-You're a really good person, Mr. Park -Hm.
Hae-kang. Your good heart was your downfall.
You won't be lonely, since you'll die together.
Mr. Park Hae-kang.
Let's be friends in our next life, instead of fighting with each
Other. I'll miss you until then.
See ya later.
Are you insane?!
You can't handle these goons by yourself.
Keep the lid on, no matter what.
Stay put, close your ears and your eyes.
There's gotta be another way.
Let me, let me talk our way out of-
Everyone! Think of your
Your parents back at home. I'm sure your parents-
-in some way, are so proud of how you -Go back inside.
Sit tight.
Your parents won't want their precious children rotting in prison, think about
-your parents. -Stop popping out. Please, be quiet.
Are you guys ready?
Mr. Kim.
Dispose of Park Hae-kang and the old man's body later. Give whoever
Survives a handsome reward.
Yes, sir.
The cash?
It's still in that truck, sir.
It's sweet smell is wafting here.
My dearest condolences to the soon to be departed.
Mr. Park Hae-kang.
Let's go.
I have to help Mr. Park
-It's us Mr. Park. -We got your back!
Damn, what took you guys so long?
You're the one who told us to wait for thirty minutes.
-Where's the old man Lizard? -The Lizard's in the barrel.
-Oh. -Damn, they beat up his handsome face!
Oh, God.
Hey guys, they tried to mess with our family.
-We should make sure they die! -We should make sure they die!
All right-
It's time to kick their ass!
We should make sure they die!
Yeah!
Ow I blocked and it still
My wrist got weak.
Hey, Big Guy, you lost weight?
It took a couple hits.
I could've still taken him down with just one,
But I got kicked by Mr. Park accidentally at the end.
Laughing's going to make the pain worse.
But hey, Lizard,
When we saw that text, we really thought you betrayed us, and it sucked.
Ugh, after all our trips to the rooftop with my life flashing before my
Eyes, do you really think I thought I wouldn't be found if I did that to you?
Come on, I'm not an idiot.
We just saved you from certain death. It's not the time to lash out.
Oh, uh, that's not what I mean. Ugh oh man, my legs are still shaking,
And my heart's still pounding.
Well, what's the plan now?
All the money is lost because I took it.
We can always get the money back.
When a person dies, we can't do the same.
We're not losing anymore
Of our family members.
Does that mean
I'm a part of the family?
All of us bled and fought together.
We're family.
We've shared a lot of meals together.
How can you still doubt us after all the meals I cooked for you?
That hurts.
We're a family alright.
Thank you.
Um should
Despite my old age I've never once properly acted like an adult for you.
But for the rest of my life,
I will be a good father to you all.
You can lean on me whenever you might be down or you're sad
And when I'm struggling
I'll lean on you all one by one like this
Lean- where'd you all go?
I'm really alright.
I also need a dab-
-Oh. -Seriously?
You're adults. You should know better than to get into fights.
Couldn't you've solved this with a little persuasion, dialogue, negotiation.
-Use your brains! -That's the one phrase I hate the most.
"Use your brains."
Oh, come on!
Did any of you stop to think that you could die there?
YOU come on. Do you realize they had our poor Lizard trapped in a barrel?
-That's enough. -Yeah, I concur.
Too much detail.
You guys used to be a gangsters? Hard to believe with how awful you fight.
Just don't go around telling other people that you were in a gang.
Ugh.
You probably don't know this being a civilian, but we used to be members of
-the legendary Oasis Gang-- -Whoa, that's not something--
President Park's back? what about our money? Where is the LRRF?
Hold on what happened to you all?
I told you to recover the LRRF,
All you brought back is this geezer?!
-Huh? -I'm deeply sorry.
Oh, for the love of, Lee, Lee Chung-won, that son of a gun!
I'm going to sue him, that's right.
I'm going to do whatever it takes till the bitter end
To get our funds back.
We have the ledger, and both Mr. Choi and I can testify, so it might be
A long shot, but we have a chance at winning.
Of course. Right.
How would we pay for this, we don't have any funds for the lawsuit.
Hey now, Yeong-jae!
Shush!
The money, we can raise, alright? How much could it possibly cost?
We'll rally.
I'll convince
All the residents,
Yeah? Don't worry 'bout it.
Let's sue him!
Sir.
Why is this becoming a bigger mess.
Excuse me, why are you clenching your fists?
Oh, um
Park Hae-kang, Park Hae-kang, Park Hae-kang, shithead!
Why's that asshole bastard have nine lives?!
Hurry up and die, hurry up, I'm sick of this
Shit!
Uh-huh.
Understood.
Chairman Lee.
It looks like the police are raiding our office.
-We're the police. -What is this about?
SEARCH AND SEIZURE WARRANT
Let's go.
Yes, I'm going in now.
Once we get what we need.
We should be able to frame him for anything.
So Commissioner Jungwon has already become their lapdog, just like
That?
And this is how they decided to kill me off?
Restrain yourself, sir.
Chairman Lee!
Mr. Kim, look at me.
There's nothing left but rage.
You know full well
Taesan's lifeline in the elders' pockets!
It's not in my hands.
What happens, happens.
Well, the public are a
Bunch of simpletons, they'll forget soon.
Don't worry about it.
You startled me.
-Chairman Lee. -Ch-chairman Lee.
What're you-
Will you gentlemen please save me.
You know that Taesan means the world to me.
I was too arrogant. I was at fault.
I'll make sure to get rid of everything in Taegowon
Including the information I have on you all.
Every piece of evidence.
Please, take this money and forgive me.
That's right.
I'm just a vulgar man who only cares about money.
I'm asking you to spare me just once.
TAEGOWON
Wait,
Last time you claimed to be with the Environmental Division.
-What do you want now? -That was for an environmental inspection.
This time, we're conducting a joint investigation into a complaint.
We're investigating because you completely ignored the order from the
Environmental Division. I'm Kang Ha-ri and I am from Complaints.
Tell me why our forum is blowing up about landfill leachate coming out
Of Taegowon!
There's nothing that we can do for you all so leave.
Well our superiors ordered us to come here, alright?!
You have five minutes.
Our time is precious!
I think they understand.
Let us in, or we'll report you for obstruction of official duties
Right away!
The more you stall, only adds more lines in our report about how you obstructed
Our investigation at the scene!
They changed their mind.
You have to leave.
-Say it again. -Hey, hey, I'll try it.
Hey.
You can't get workers comp if you're hurt protecting your superiors.
Open the gate before things get really ugly.
-That sounded cool. -Hey.
-Are you scared? -Not at all.
-Nice try, Mr. Doong-hui. -Open the gate please.
Nice try.
Mr. Park.
I apologize about what happened
To Yong-man.
You know better than anyone
Exactly who it was that ended his life.
Let's not do this.
That case has been closed already.
What's this?
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY MR. SON I NEED TO LINE MY BOYS' POCKETS
INVESTMENT EXPENDITURE
Ugh, you little shit.
Hey, why are you bringing this to me now?
Why didn't you decide to blackmail me before this?
I had to be strategic about the timing.
You would have framed my boys for everything
And mysteriously disappeared.
Like you, I've been letting it accrue interest.
What is it you want?
Let us through. Whoever doesn't cooperate will be arrested on the spot for
Obstruction of official duties. Open up. Move aside!
I said move aside!
I'll bet you that's Mr. Park working his
-magic! -Step aside!
Outta the way.
Dig a little deeper over there.
-Deeper. -Did you find anything?
-Uh, not yet, sir. -Nothing at all?
Correct.
What about you?
-I found something. -What is this?
Oh! We found a body!
-Contact headquarters. -Yes, sir.
-Did you hear that too? -Oh, my God.
Keep digging everyone!
Another one over here!
-Here too! -Here's another one, sir!
This isn't good.
-It's time to go. -Come on.
SEO GANG-WON
What the hell are they all doing in my playground?
They assured us
That there would be no further investigation beyond a search and
Seizure of company headquarters.
I think
We should leave the premises.
PARK HAE-KANG
Taegowon's landscaping looked a little dull
So I dug up the ground a little. It's much better.
So it was you, Park Hae-kang.
I hope you're impressed by it.
I built this beautiful playground piece by piece,
Bleeding for it with every step.
It was my life's work
At Taegowon, owned by Chairman Lee Chung-won of Taesan Construction,
Twelve sets of human remains were found in a mass grave.
The police have classified this as a serial murder, corpse
Abandonment case abandonment case
Park Hae-kang thinks he's some kind of genius.
Look at the ugly mess I'm in all because of that man.
A hangnail I didn't remove.
Breaking news.
TAESAN GROUP OUT "HANMIN CONSTRUCTION" NEW CONTRACT FOR OMAN NEW TOWN DEVELOPMENT
Concerned, The Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, and Transport
Has announced
Taesan was the main contractor for the Oman New Town project,
Now contracted to Hanmin Construction.
With this unexpected turn of events, it seems that Taesan Construction will be
Excluded from all current and future public projects.
Whoosh!
-Chairman Lee Chung-won of Taesan -Woosh!
Construction, who is suspected of serial murder, has apparently gone into
The police believe he may be trying to smuggle himself out of the nation
-and are focusing their efforts to -He can try to smuggle himself out,
-but he's still on earth. -search for him on coastal areas,
Ports, and ferry terminals along South Korea's east and south coasts
What I wouldn't give for a little break, buns to the sun beach time.
Hey, Big Guy, we're not done yet.
We're never done. Like "The Never-Ending Story."
-Did you learn English? -A little from Gyeong-buk.
-Hey there, Gyeong-buk. -Woosh.
Hm?
APPOINTMENT LETTER PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
Mr. Park Hae-kang.
Meet me on the rooftop of the penthouse, it has a such nice breeze.
Hey, Lee Chung-won!
You're quick, as I expected.
Did you think
Oh, come on, just how evil do you think I am?
Gyeong-buk is back at home safe and sound.
Here's the 17.8 billion.
You were so desperate to get your hands on it.
You can have it.
My life's work has been destroyed, so all this money,
Means no more than
Scraps of paper to me.
Take it, get out there,
And become a hero to everybody.
While you do what?
What?
You've got the wrong idea.
I was just quite fond of you, Mr. Park.
Besides,
You and I are practically twins.
We're practically twins?
You and I?
We both ended up crawling our way here following the cash.
We're alike,
You and I.
We're different.
Although I was here for the money,
Unlike you,
It was to protect what's mine, while you took from others.
We are not alike.
That's just how life works.
Someone becomes the victim left behind so the other one can win.
Then enlighten me as to why
You're hiding out if you're the winner?
I'm standing right here, aren't I?
Taesan is still Taesan
And I'll be out in half a day.
Life is never that easy.
Pitiful little
Lee Chung-won.
You're pitying me?
Park Yong-man
That old fool,
Also looked at me the same way you are.
Ah,
I feel sorry for you.
As he was laying there, dying,
He looked at me with so much pity in his eyes.
I hated that look so goddamn much that
I personally
Cut off the stupid old man's air supply
With a knife I was using to cut an apple.
Like candy from a baby.
Stab me.
That's it.
That's it. Do it.
You're dying to kill me.
I'm sure you've stabbed a lot of people, you goddamn gangster.
Do it, Park Hae-kang.
Stab me in the heart!
You're someone
Who instinctively tries to judge right from wrong.
Don't hesitate on my account or make bad decisions because of me.
What are you stalling?
Why are you staring?
I said, stab me, asshole!
Park Hae-kang!
No thanks.
If I stab you here,
Your death will be too quick.
That's no way to punish anyone.
I'm starting to see why Park Yong-man pitied you now.
You just
Never learned how to be a decent human being or live like one.
Don't give me that bullshit!
Stop spouting nonsense and stab me Park Hae-kang!
What the hell are you doing?
Why did you stop being fun!?
This is how you live a fun life!
This money
Goes back to where it belongs.
You may have built this complex
But it's not yours.
And you weren't my match.
I was always one step ahead.
Did you see the news?
Chairman Lee turned himself in to the police!
What do you think is going to happen to our LRRF now?
If he tells us we have no recourse, we're done for.
Do you think we'll even get paid this month President Jang?
That's what I've been saying. It's just- Does he think we're done just because he
Hid the money and went to jail? Ugh,
-I can't believe someone that awful -I know, right? Ugh, I know!
-Exists. -Knock, knock!
-Oh, my my, President Park! -Clear the way it's heavy!
-President Park! -Oh, careful.
-What is this? -One, two, three.
-Are you alright? -I mean, what is
Don't tell me. Did you-did you actually
Steal our LRRF back from Lee Chung-won?
I simply recovered it. He's the one
-that stole it. Open it, open the bag. -Oh, woah.
Oh.
Oh, oh, my!
Pr-president Park, I'm not dreaming, right? This
President Park, should we announce publicly right away? They're all
Gonna lose their minds!
My hands are shaking! Should-should I reprint all of our bills?
Wait, hold on!
Now, we need to check how much is in there.
And then gather
The bankbook, the documents, the seal and hurry to the bank!
-Uh-huh, right. -Oh!
-Okay. -Let's go! Hurry, hurry.
We recovered the LRRF!
Good heavens, I can't believe it!
Come on gather everything up, get it all
-together. -It's really heavy!
President Park!
You worked so hard.
President Park, thank you so much for what you've done.
President Jang, I found the bankbook!
I should go to the bank right away, alright?
President Park,
Stay safe out there.
PATIENT LEE * WON
I'll take your temperature now, sir.
Thank you.
It took you longer than I thought.
Were you all too busy deciding who would get
To hold my leash?
Sorry I took longer than you expected.
I'm here to deliver a message from the elders.
"You're our little fall guy".
That's their message.
Of course it is.
They have to cut off the tail
So that the body can live, after all.
That's the only way you'll have a chance at a pardon later.
I'd advise keeping your mouth shut
That's just to prevent us all from getting killed.
Hey, Commisioner Kwak.
I have poured so much money into this endeavor
And disposed of so many bodies
Just to be abandoned?
That's why I'm here actually.
If this were to get out, it would spell doom for all of the elders.
And were that to happen, your lifeline would be cut off, too.
Am I wrong about that?
What is it you want?
Mm
Shut my trap.
Enough to keep my loose lips from singing.
Wow, our dear, dear, commissioner
How transparent.
You surprised me, you know that?
Keeps go in the box, and throw discards in the sack.
I mean, considering all the hard work we put into this, we should
Have something to show for it.
We spent more on pain relief patches than what we actually made.
Ugh, whose bright idea was it to embezzle the LRRF within three months again?
Embezzle, my ass.
My bones are aching from returning what someone else stole.
My poor joints. What? Are we really throwing these out?
Discard sack for both!
And add mine.
We've been through too much to keep them, the memories of our labor makes me
-wanna puke! -Evidence of our darkest timelines.
Hey, Big Guy,
You're the one who bought these, it's okay?
That color is really pretty.
I'm over it. Toss.
Alright, toss em!
Don't toss. We need to wear them again.
Where?
Are you going to wear them around the neighborhood while you're saying goodbye?
Now, where might we wear them?
I'm not sure.
PROSECUTOR GENERAL CHOI SEUNG-HO
Yes, Prosecutor, I'm here now.
Keep your mouth shut.
There are plenty of holes in your doings to exploit, don't forget.
The storm will pass, hold out until then, alright?
-Let it blow over. -Yes Prosecutor.
Oh, boy.
That's quite a crowd.
Eun-ho.
Looks like you'll have your work cut out for you
Once I get arrested.
Don't worry about me, sir.
Come back safe and sound.
I'll be able to handle things here.
Yep.
I won't be in there very long.
Let's go.
Here he comes!
-He's arrived. -There he is.
Do you admit to the charges?
Are you denying the charges?
Were you directly involved in the case?
Are you denying that you had anything to do with the bodies found at Taegowon?
I'm here to apologize to the public for causing concern.
It wasn't my intention.
The allegations against me have no ground to stand on.
I will cooperate fully with the prosecution
To uncover the truth
No matter what.
To the public once again, I sincerely apologize.
Who was behind Taegowon?
Chairman Lee. Are you denying the charges?
Hello there!
Chairman Lee Chung-won,
Sorry we're late!
We demand the media render a judgment on
TRUE VALUE RESIDENTS' REPRESENTATIVE COUNCIL PRESIDENT PARK HAE-KANG
-this man! -Hello, everyone!
-This man! -Hello, everyone!
Chairman Lee Chung-won, it's a bit too soon to be saying goodbye.
And you are?
Hello, I'm
Park Hae-kang.
The True Value State Resident Representative Council President.
What are you doing?
Drag the bastard out of here right now.
Drag him.
I promised, didn't I?
I told you I'd be tearing you off myself.
Today is the day.
Cue the audio!
Park Yong-man. I personally
Cut off the stupid old man's air supply
With a knife I was using to cut an apple. Like candy from a baby.
Every single word of that is fake!
It's fake? Then how about this?
We've got some very crisp footage.
I'm on it!
These people are so funny.
They go on and on about the law, justice, and whatnot,
Yet they all have at least one person they so desperately want to kill.
I just simply
Became a knife for them that's all.
As for Song U-sik's involvement,
The victim of his hit-and-run accident made threats.
He said he would get the police involved, didn't he.
Taegowon became that victim's burial ground.
U-sik held onto his position because of me.
Mu-murder?
Is this true?
I can't let you do this. It's going be too dangerous of a mission.
I can do it, I spent years as a cosplay part-timer.
Oh, watch out, are you okay!?
They're beating up people just to destroy the evidence! See that?
You just pushed an old man, you're out of line!
Oh, so they're trying to destroy the evidence, is that it?
Film this, film it! Film everything they're doing!
Park Hae-kang!
You I'm going to kill you, you hear that?
You hear that?!
This is your own doing.
Don't worry, you'll have your friends with you.
Let go, damn it!
They're taking him in.
-We did it! -Yeah!
-Yeah! -We did it!
-Yes! -Oh
Oh, man, that felt amazing!
You're the greatest!
What if we really end up on the news because of this? I gotta hide, I gotta
Hide!
Did you see the look on his face?! And when Lizard rolled?!
-Just in case! -In that color?!
President, are you done with all this now?
Okay, let's get outta here. Back to being Park Hae-kang,
Not President Park.
Ah, it's finally over.
We're done!
-We're done! -We're done!
-We won, we won! We won, we won! -Yeah!
-Yeah! Winner winner chicken dinner! -Yeah!
-Winners! -We won! We wo-on!
Yeah! We won!
BLUE HOUSE
ARREST WARRANT
SUPREME COURT OF KOREA
Hey, let's hurry.
Mr. Choi, please open the door!
PROSECUTOR GENERAL CHOI SEUNG-HO
I'm coming out, damn, hold your horses.
DISAPPEARANCE OF SEONGDONG-GU HIT-AND-RUN VICTIM
Man, our president really is insane.
He aired that live in front of the prosecutor's office and media.
Wow, that determination.
He's really something else.
I'm getting major goosebumps.
I mean think about it!
Chairman Lee Chung-won used to bring us snacks with that gentle face of his!
Ah,
We're all recharged.
Huh?
Now, let's all stop watching the fire,
And get back
To working, okay?
-Mm-hmm. -Let's get rid of all the corruption
In our entire complex,
And get True Value
To how it was. A normal place.
We got this!
-We, we've got this! -We've got this!
-We've got this! -We've got this. Yay! Get to work!
-Get moving everyone. -Let's get back to work.
-Go team! -Go team!
Move, move.
Gyeong-buk, you're awake?
Mm-hmm. Guess what.
I rode the swings at the playground with your friend, Uncle.
Gyeong-buk, what did my friend say?
-Mm -Gyeong-buk, you're so lucky.
So many people are protecting you.
I'm a little jealous.
In all my years
Nobody, not ever once,
Has someone protected me.
I've never had anybody like that.
He looked so sad, that I wanted to ask him if he would like to share some
Of my ice cream, but
He left before I could.
That friend of mine
Wasn't sad because he didn't have anyone to protect him.
Why then?
He was sad because
He didn't know how to protect others.
Does that mean you're the happiest person?
-Hm? -You have so many of us to protect, Uncle.
-Hee-hee. -You're right.
I sure protect a lot of people, don't I?
Hee-hee.
Gyeong-buk is protected.
Ah. I have to pee.
You asleep?
Not yet.
You were born when I was six years old.
I was an only child, and I got all of Mom and Dad's love for myself.
And then you were born.
All of a sudden it felt like Mom and Dad's world revolved around you.
So I used to hate you a lot.
I know.
You used to pinch me when I was asleep,
And take my toys when you thought that Mom wasn't watching.
Dunked my favorite shoes in the mud,
And doodled on my favorite dolls with a marker when I wasn't around.
Oh, woah, you actually remember all that?
But after Mom and Dad passed away
You were always there for me.
I was afraid that if I kept treating you so badly,
That they might take my last family member away.
I'm aware I'm the reason you kept working so much.
You paid for my studies by working as an account manager,
You dabbled in illegal work
Just to support your kid sister.
You're not the reason that I started doing things like that.
If anything,
You're what kept me going when I wanted to give up in life.
The time and sleepless nights you sacrificed
Out of love for me
Completely outweigh all the time you spent hating.
So
Leave it to me and don't be scared.
I'll take care of you this time.
You just concentrate on putting your life back on track.
Mm-hmm, okay I will.
Are you crying?
Ugh, I'm not.
Just hurry up and go to sleep.
SEOUL JUNGNANG POLICE STATION
Ha-jeong.
Tell them everything they want.
Cooperate with them and be sure to seek leniency first
And if that doesn't work,
Make them feel sorry for you.
-If that doesn't work then-- -Ha-ri.
Stop worrying so much,
Okay?
Make sure that you become a lawyer.
Take care of me in my old age.
Mr. Choi.
Ugh, come on, don't dawdle.
Ha-jeong, ma'am?
I'll work hard and when you come back to us,
I will be a new Man-go.
-"A new man-go." -Why'd he say that?
Let's go.
You're still here?
Here's a petition from the residents and a lawyer's contact.
She'll be out of there in no time at all.
Thank you so much Mr. Park.
Thank you, you've been great,
Ms. Kang Ha-ri.
Oh, my goodness, oh, it's so heavy!
Why do you have so many books that you don't even read?
Wow, it's finally starting to sink in after seeing all these boxes.
I'd say it's bittersweet but it's not.
It's just making me sad.
It felt so cramped when everything was going on, but now it's giant.
Why don't we take a picture before we leave?
A family picture, yeah?
Why a family photo all of a sudden?
How's my hair?
I like it! Hee-hee!
All right,
A commemorative photo together.
To the window!
-We don't really need to take a photo. -Let's see.
-Hey -You get so tense around cameras.
-Hold on. You have a gray hair. I'm gonna -What do I do with my hands? My hair's
-pluck it. -sticking out.
-Yeah because you kept stressing me out! -How should daddy pose? Show me how to
Make a heart?
I started the timer.
Hey.
Come over here Father. This way.
"Father"?
-Father. -"Father".
Stop crying, look at the camera and smile.
Smile, Dad.
Mm-hmm.
Laugh for the final shot!
-One two kimchi! -Everyone laugh!
GOODBYE PHOENIX THE LATE PARK YONG-MAN
So I'm back.
I'm here, Father.
You're not here to reject it anymore.
So I get to call you whatever I want.
I'm
Done with all my revenge, at last.
Did I do good?
I'm um
I'm going somewhere soon.
For a long time.
So while I'm gone
Please keep a tight leash,
Don't let our family get into any more trouble.
Hm?
3 YEARS LATER
I mean
Come on, Mr. Choi, can you try to hurry it along.
This is harder than all of my work at the apartment.
Would it kill you to stop rushing me, Ms. Ha-jeong?
Hmm?
I'm doing the best that I can.
FINE FLOUR BAKERY
Good morning.
-Hi there! -Oh, you're here.
You know I always come here before work.
No other breakfast is as good as your bread, Ms. Kang.
You think so?
I really am
So grateful for all the True Value residents that come here.
It's because your bread is delicious. We're neighbors,
As well, right?
Mr. Choi, you look you're a bit happier
-here. -Oh, you noticed?
I'll take mine to go this morning, thank you.
Oh, right.
What would you like?
Uh
-She's in a rush Mr. Choi, hurry. -Oh, okay.
Wow, sold out?
Don't do that. I told you I'd take care of it.
Did you have a good trip? Where's Gyeong-buk?
English academy. His pronunciation is great.
Oh.
I told him the "man-go" pun. He said I wasn't pronouncing it right. "It's
Mango".
I guess puns aren't his thing, but English is.
Gyeong-buk is so smart, we'll have to make a lot of money to support
His schooling, huh.
I'll
Open up more bakery branches to support us
Just let me handle everything.
All you have to do is bake your heart out.
What the heck?
Oh. Aren't you running late?
Huh?
Nah, it's alright. I'll finish this and leave.
-I got it. -No, I got it.
-No, I go tit. -What? I got it.
Let's do it together. We got it, we got it.
Together? I got it, you got it!
So this would be
SAFETY MANAGEMENT OF MULTI-FAMILY HOUSING
Hey,
Is that middle aged returning student who's been winning all the
Scholarships? Huh?
Why's that man returning to school at
-his age? -Which would make this
Be careful. I heard a rumor. That guy used to be a big time gangster.
I heard he has a tattoo.
That's the rumor going around.
See you there at eight.
-I don't think he was a gangster. -Mm.
Oh. I need to remember
First time seeing a big time gangster, study?
If you want to get a scholarship, spend more time reading and less time
Gossiping.
I'm watching the two of you.
Ugh, what did I tell you? He admitted he was in a gang.
What's wrong with me?
That was sexy as hell.
Big Guy.
That's your third one today.
You've completely thrown off our vegetable costs for this month.
You're fired, okay?
Stop coming to work.
You can't fire me, boss.
Hm? Why can't I do that?
Article 26 of the Labor Standards Act, which covers the advance notice of
Dismissal? You didn't give me a month's notice,
So if you want to fire me, you have to pay me 30 days' pay in lieu of notice
Upfront. I'm afraid that's your only option.
-Hey, listen here, you freaking-- -I have a lot of friends in the legal
Field so I know my stuff. So um before I get in touch with the
Ministry of Employment and Labor,
Hurry up and give me more salmon toppings.
Huh?
See you there at eight.
Save mine for later!
Hey. Come back where are you going, huh?
I'm not telling.
LAW OFFICE JEONGSAN
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR GRAND OPENING PRESIDENT PARK
I'm sure I wrote it down somewhere, where is it
I'll find it later.
Wow, you really did it this time, sir!
You're here.
So this is what you were talking about? What!?
How and when did you set up all this though?
An entire office?!
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR NEW BUSINESS, SIR
I spent all three years in there thinking about this.
That's why I'm glad you guys are here.
It was the first part of my plan.
How is it? You boys impressed?
I got goosebumps!
When I think about all the nosebleeds I got over the past three years thanks to
-your plan -Oh, yeah.
I'll order double the salary.
Now, since we had a nice, long break for three years, let's start warming up,
-again okay? Yup. -Yes, sir!
You're all here.
-Sister-in-law! -Oh, brother-in-law!
Whoa, how did you talk Ms. Kang into joining us all here?
I did no such thing.
I scouted her.
Yeong-ju, I got scolded again.
I don't think I'm cut out for this.
I should find another line of work-
Ugh I was just-
Woah!
Mr. Park Hae-kang!
Your badge looks real nice.
Ms. Kang Ha-ri, the lawyer.
What's going on?
I don't take on casual part-timer work like I used to.
Thought you should know.
Let's start a business together.
Like I would?
I'm a real lawyer now.
I have nothing to gain from getting involved with you again.
I have an accounting license now. Thought you should know.
But
Because of my criminal record, I can't stamp a document for five years.
Which brings me to my point. I would like to borrow your license.
What do you mean by that?
Please be my legal shield, I promise it'll be worth it.
The name of my business is "Law Office Jeongsan."
Um, what was that?
Uh- did you say law office?
I handle the accounting, and you shield us with the law.
A win-win for us both.
That's not a win. I've just gotten my career off the ground, and you
Want me to join up with you?
How about a seventy-thirty split. I get seventy.
What about if the two of us never meet again.
Five-o, Five-o.
Cool.
And that was your partnership's day one?
Melodrama.
Hey, read the room for once, man.
Yeah but a fifty-fifty split is a great deal, isn't it, Ms. Kang?
Ugh, after paying off the loan interest on this place, I'll just be a
Part-timer with a law license.
THE CENTRAL BAY MAINTENANCE FEE CORRUPTION AUDIT
Why don't we get started?
Surprise!
-Oh, sir! -It's our dad!
-I can't believe you're here! -Did you break out of prison?
What are you talking about? Inspired by Deaconess Park from the Frontier Church,
I repented and was released three months early for good behavior!
-Hallelujah! -But you're a Buddhist?
-Ah, what? -Whatever, it's the perfect timing!
I told you I'd be able to get you out in about three years.
Oh, my, thank you, Ms. Kang.
Where do I sit?
Oh, there's a spot!
Mr. Park,
What do ya say?
Why don't we start with
Discussing my salary?
-You know it's performance- based, right? -Oh, shoot!
Welcome.
Gather up everyone.
-Let's. -Yep.
Why's this office so dark?
Take your glasses off.
Woah. Oh, you're stunning.
Here.
Let's settle the accounts properly.
-Yes, sir! -Yes, sir!
-Mm. -It matches, right?
Yes, it's correct.
It's so reassuring to bring you with us, President Cha.
Right.
The residents entrusted us with their money,
This is the least we can do for them all.
BANK BOOK
Why don't we head over to our management office.
Sounds good right?
-Right. -Shall we?
Did you see the new kindergarten
-they built? I mean it's really insane. -Mm-hmm.
Yeah well, that thing is so secure, that it could probably withstand an
-earthquake. -Mm-hmm.
I know Ever since Taesan hired a professional manager, they built
Us a new kindergarten, and they even took charge of the apartment
Reinforcement construction.
I'm so proud of all the hard work we've put in so far.
It's a shame they built us a sturdy kindergarten, after our kids are in
-elementary school. -Yeah.
I agree with you there.
Why don't you have another one.
Ah, wait, I brought something. Here.
What's this?
Look at this.
Listen, as you girls already know, I used to really slam my in-laws, the
Construction at our apartment, and a whole bunch of random stuff
-all on my YouTube channel Except- -Mm-hmm.
Girls I love love
This product.
Ta-da.
You said your poor knees were stiff, and your wrists hurt, right? This is
-perfect for that, just you wait. -Mm-hmm.
My shoulders have been aching so much lately, so this is perfect.
My younger sister just had twins, and she also told me her joints are
Aching all over. I should get her one of these.
-Totally. -I want try this. You don't mind right?
No, not at all, try one. It's top tier.
It goes right down the hatch.
PRESIDENT JANG SUK-JIN PRESIDENT CHA YUN-JO
I mean, how could he do this to us?
Hm?
We worked our butts off for the past three years
And it felt as though we had finally managed to make an apartment
Worth living in, only for Mr. Choi, that jerk-
Just to hit us over the head with this!
Looking at him, you would think he's so gentle and innocent he wouldn't even
Hurt a fly!
But while he was holding the facility manager's seal in his grubby little
Hands,
He switched the pages thinking nobody would notice.
It remember it was a standard contract when we signed it,
But the original copy that was sent to the company was full of toxic clauses.
Exactly! The penalty clause alone stipulates six hundred million! We never
Would've signed the contract! He thinks that we're a couple of idiots!
The penalty's 600 million won.
It's not like we can sue him.
We can't sue him?
Yes we can.
Let me take the lead on this one.
TRUE VALUE STATE 3RD RESIDENTS' REPRESENTATIVE COUNCIL
The head of the administration caused trouble and ran away, this contract's
Null and void! Why should we take responsibility for his actions?
I agree with you but the contractors are already camped out in the management
Office.
They're all making a huge fuss, and they're demanding the entire six
Hundred.
That's what I'm saying.
On top of that, the law says it's on us to prove their corruption. That's
Next to impossible.
The residents need to calm down. The unit representatives are being accused of
Being in on it. They're all banding together and refusing to pay what
They owe as their maintenance fees.
Only three years ago, we recovered 17.8 billion stolen from our apartment.
And now, we're getting screwed by one administrative manager. How does
That make any sense at all?
Yeah but we had President Park with us back then, though. What are we going
To do about that 600 million penalty?
We can't just take this lying down.
We're dealing with professional conmen.
Our only hope is to hire professionals as well.
Allow me to introduce
The experts helping us.
Come on in.
This place hasn't changed at all.
I heard you're being cheated out of 600 million.
Pr-pr-president Park!
-President Park, what brings you here? -Oh!
Hello, everyone.
I'm Park Hae-kang, the head of the Apartment Corruption Audit
Department at Law Office Jeongsan.
I'm Ms. Kang Ha-ri the head attorney. Don't worry because as of today,
We're the special legal representatives of True Value State.
-She must have really become a lawyer. -I'm glad they're helping us.
We have confirmed that fifty million won
In apartment kickbacks was deposited into the nominee account of the runaway
Mr. Choi.
Contracts made through a breach of trust are legally invalid,
Which means that you won't owe them any money.
We've sent out a notice of contract invalidation with the evidence we
Just obtained. It goes
Into immediate effect starting right about now.
Immediately. You heard that right?
We don't have to worry!
-I am so relieved, thank God. -Yes!
Starting tomorrow those companies are banned from entering. In exchange,
I'll start conducting a month long special audit of this apartment.
Do I have your consent?
-Yes, a thousand times yes! -Of course he does.
-He has all of our consent of course! -You're welcome here!
Oh, wow, oh, wow.
Wow, We're back here of all places.
You dangled me from that roof.
-Oof! -Don't forget.
Ooh, that was scary!
Hey, by the way,
Three years ago or today,
Apartments are just not that cost-effective.
We cleaned up True Value, and now it's turning into a dump. How can we just
Watch? Let's offer an after-sales service.
That sounds good. Who would put up with their yard turning into a dump? Not me
That's for damn sure.
But there are so many numbers on each page of a ledger.
I bet they'll try to slash our fees.
Then I'll make sure to attach all the receipts and bill them for everything.
Oh, it's so complicated. I'll leave the ledger up to you guys. I'm going
To catch that runaway Mr. Choi and just squeeze the heck outta that guy.
And, to celebrate our first client,
As Law Office Jeongsan, our dinner tonight is all on me!
Wow.
Cool!
-Yeah! -All right!
-Woohoo! -Ooh, thank you Ms. Kang!
Can I order the most expensive thing on the menu?
-Happy to do it! -Marbled ribeye for the win!
Is that what you want?!
Yeah!
THE APARTMENT JOB
-Alright! -Ooh maybe I should too!
-Alright! -Not me, I've got enough room!
And then to norebang for the second round!
THE APARTMENT JOB